# Khoi Vu

Address: West Jordan, Utah 84088

Cell: (385) 231-7667

Email: vu.khoi6111@gmail.com

Portfolio: kvureactportfolio.herokuapp.com

Github: github.com/ChefKhoiRD

Full stack web developer utilizing real world customer service experience to build web applications with a user-first approach. Earned a certificate from full stack development from Trilogy Coding Bootcamp at the University of Utah. Now equipped with web development skills in Javascript, HTML, CSS, and MERN stack technologies. I focus on creating innovative apps by adapting, working with, and learning about the newest technologies within the field.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### Oct 2020 - Sep 2022 || Ruth's Chris Steak House Server Assistant

- Remains calm and poised during high-volume shifts while maintaining exceptional service quality.
- Self-motivated service industry professional willing to assist team members with completing tasks to keep operations running smoothly.
- Reliable candidate ready to take on challenges using problem-solving and task prioritization skills to help team succeed.

## Mar 2017 - Mar 2020 || Rollz Restaurant Assistant Manager

- · Decisive yet personable problem-solver with superior conflict resolution skills.
- Excellent verbal and written communicator with strong background cultivating positive relationships and exceeding goals.
- Results-driven professional, enhances operational success with forward-thinking approaches and skilled support of senior management initiatives.

# Nov 2016 - Jan 2017 || Shabu Shabu Restaurant Dining Room Attendant

- · Greet guests and serve all needs with friendly, fast support.
- Good at troubleshooting problems and building successful solutions.

#### SKILLS

- · Javascript
- React
- · HTML
- · CSS
- MySQL
- · Node.js
- · GraphQL
- · Sequelize
- · Express.is
- · MongoDB
- · MERN Stack

#### **EDUCATION AND OUALIFICATIONS**

May 2022 - Oct 2022 || University of Utah Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Development